Hector?
赫克托
-Kid? -Oh, Hector!
-孩子  -哦 赫克托
You are right, I should have gone back to my family.
你是对的 我应该回家
They told me not to be like De La Cruz. But I didn't listen.
她们告诉我不要学德拉库斯 但是我不听
-Hey, It's okay. -I told them I didn't care if they remember me.
-没事的   -我告诉她们我不在乎她们是否记得我
I didn't care if I was on the stupid ofrenda.
也不在乎我是不是能上那个什么祭坛
Hey, chamaco. It's okay.  It's okay.
没事的 孩子
I told them I didn't care.
我告诉他们我不在乎
Hector.
赫克托
Hector?
She's forgetting me.
她要把我忘记了
Who?
谁
My daughter.
我女儿
She is the reason you wanted to cross the bridge.
她就是你想要过桥的原因
I just wanted to see her again.
我就是想再看看她​
I never should have left Santa Cecilia.
我不该离开桑塔西西莉亚​
I wish I could apologize.
我希望我可以道歉
I wish I could tell her that her papa was trying to come home.
我希望告诉她 她的爸爸一直想回家的
That he loved her so much.
还想告诉她 她的爸爸非常爱她
My Coco.
我的可可
Coco?
可可